med-u.org 2009-10-01

# medU | About Us

## Please review this privacy policy carefully before using the site.

This site (“Site” or “case Sites” ) is owned and operated by The Institute for Innovative Technology In Medical Education ("iInTIME"), a 501(c)(3) organized under the laws of the State of New Hampshire. The purpose of this Site is to make available iInTIME's virtual patient cases designed to comprehensively teach the core third-year curriculum to individuals involved in health care education and practice.

iInTIME is committed to fair information practices. iInTIME also respects the privacy and security of its users. To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this statement disclosing our privacy practices. Here, you will learn what personal identifying information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose it to any person or organization outside iInTIME. However, in connection with its educational mission, iInTIME does share information of the usage of those users who are authorized to use the site because of their affiliation with a subscribing institution with such institutions. See below for more details.

## Information We Collect and How We Use It

iInTIME collects certain information from and about its users in three ways: directly from the user, from our Web server logs, and with cookies.

Information from the User: When you register to use the Site, we will ask you for personal information such as your name, institution, and e-mail address. Each time you log on to the Site, we associate the information tracked with the user who has logged in. We also use this personal information to provide online technical support and troubleshooting to you.

In the course of using the Site, you may upload or transmit or submit answers or reactions to the case simulations that you are presented with. Such information is collected and stored.

If you are subscribing as an individual, we will request financial information (e.g., What is your credit card number?). Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the subscription purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider.

Web server logs: When you visit a case Site, we track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

  * your Internet protocol address
  * the name of your Internet service provider
  * the state or country from which you accessed the Site
  * what kind of browser or computer you use
  * the date and time of your visit
  * the Web page you linked to our site from
  * the pages you viewed on the site
  * the number of links you click within the Site
  * the amount of time spent at each page and what you clicked on the page, including any answers clicked on the page.

Cookies: The case Sites use cookies (i.e., small bits of text that our servers place into a file on your computer's hard drive). These are used to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on our Site.

## Information Shared with Third Parties

iInTIME will not share information it collects which personally identifies you or the personal information you provide upon subscription, registration or log-in with third parties except as follows:

  * With agents and contractors who use it on iInTIME's behalf or in connection with their relationship with us and the operation, administration and maintenance of the Site.
  * In the case of Authorized Users who have access to the site through a Subscribing Institution, with your Subscribing Institution (as described further below).
  * At your specific request.

iInTIME does not share information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes unless you expressly ask us to. iInTIME may share information which does not identify you personally in connection with its research and development of its products and in connection with its operation, administration and maintenance of the site. The type of information used for such research, development and administration may include summary statistics about traffic and usage patterns, non-identifiable user submissions and related site information.

Additional Use of Information: The case Sites may at some point make chat rooms, forums, message boards or news groups available to you. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas is public. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Don't disclose information in these public forums that might be considered confidential. In addition, the case Sites may also provide a discussion forum and interactivity features that use personal identification information.

### Links to Other Companies' Sites

The Site may link to sites maintained by companies that are not affiliated with iInTIME. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites, and we encourage you to use caution when visiting them. In particular, we recommend you view the privacy policy posted on each site.

### How to Correct Inaccuracies

If you've registered for iInTIME Virtual Patient, you can access and update your information by contacting [[info@i-intime.org](mailto:info@i-intime.org)](mailto:info@i-intime.org) .

## Information of “Individual Subscribers” and “Authorized Users”

Individual Subscribers: Certain individuals ("Individual Subscribers") subscribe individually to receive access to the Site or portions thereof. We collect personal information from these users and track their usage of the Site but will not share such information with third parties except as described in the Section above. Such users should be aware that to receive credit for their use of the Site, they may need to share information regarding usage with institutions from which they wish to receive credit.

Authorized Users: Certain individuals ("Authorized Users") have access to the Site, or portions thereof, as a result of their affiliation with an institution subscribing to the Site, in particular institutions providing health care education. iInTIME collects personal identification information and tracks all usage of the Site by such users and provides usage data, including data identified with particular Authorized Users, to that Authorized User's Subscribing Institution. Such information may also be shared with some state accreditation agencies if required.

### How We Protect Your Information

iInTIME uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. For example, when we ask customers to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.

### Privacy Policy Changes

If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post and highlight the policy changes.

### Questions?

Please send an e-mail message to [[info@i-intime.org](mailto:info@i-intime.org)](mailto:info@i-intime.org) .
